<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Design solution on Building Sustainable Solutions on Azure</title>
    <link>https://wiigg.dev/bssazure/design/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Design solution on Building Sustainable Solutions on Azure</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 23:32:48 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wiigg.dev/bssazure/design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Architect a solution</title>
      <link>https://wiigg.dev/bssazure/design/architect/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 12:47:04 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wiigg.dev/bssazure/design/architect/index.html</guid>
      <description>Directions Use the discussion questions to guide your architecture. As a team, build a diagram illustrating how the customer’s existing structure can be made sustainable using sustainable best practices. Requirements:
Include all the elements from Step 1 to build your solution. Include candidate roadmap components and explain which will be introduced to the current architectural landscape. Resolve the changes across the architecture landscape: what will be removed, retired and/or maintained. Tip You can use PowerPoint or any other tool: Visio, Draw.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Checklist</title>
      <link>https://wiigg.dev/bssazure/design/checklist/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 23:32:48 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wiigg.dev/bssazure/design/checklist/index.html</guid>
      <description>At the end of this step, teams should have a proposed solution diagram that meets the following requirements:
Illustrates how the customer’s existing structure can be made sustainable in Azure using sustainable best practices. Includes all the elements from Step 1. Includes candidate roadmap components and explains which will be introduced to the current architectural landscape. Resolves the changes across the architecture landscape: what will be removed, retired and/or maintained. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://wiigg.dev/bssazure/design/resources/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 12:50:12 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wiigg.dev/bssazure/design/resources/index.html</guid>
      <description> Emissions Impact Dashboard Microsoft Cloud for Sustainability The Planetary Computer Principles of Sustainable Software Engineering Reactor: Green Tech Series Green Software Foundation Azure Architecture Center </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>