<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Optimise architecture on Building Sustainable Solutions on Azure</title>
    <link>https://wiigg.dev/bssazure/optimise/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Optimise architecture on Building Sustainable Solutions on Azure</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 12:50:19 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wiigg.dev/bssazure/optimise/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Apply WAF practices</title>
      <link>https://wiigg.dev/bssazure/optimise/waf/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 12:47:56 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wiigg.dev/bssazure/optimise/waf/index.html</guid>
      <description>Directions Discuss the following questions: What does well-architected mean at Microsoft? What is the difference between Cloud Adoption Framework (CAF) and Well Architected Framework (WAF)? What are the five pillars of Microsoft Azure Well-Architected framework? How does WAF contribute to a solution’s overall sustainability profile? As a team, perform an assessment of the team’s proposed solution architecture from Step 2 using the WAF assessment questions. Discuss the following questions: Are there any additional questions that should be part of the assessment, especially when it comes to building sustainable practices?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Checklist</title>
      <link>https://wiigg.dev/bssazure/optimise/checklist/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 12:47:56 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wiigg.dev/bssazure/optimise/checklist/index.html</guid>
      <description>As a team, you should have the following slides:
Confirmation that the proposed solution is following best practices and patterns for sustainability and other measures. Description of how this confirmation is done. Summary of the design methodology that your solution will implement to measure, track, and optimise energy usage and emissions over time. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://wiigg.dev/bssazure/optimise/resources/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 12:50:19 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wiigg.dev/bssazure/optimise/resources/index.html</guid>
      <description> Azure Well Architected Framework Sustainability Workload Documentation Sustainability Workload Assessment Cloud Adoption Framework for Azure Azure Well Architected Review Assessment </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>