<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Overview on Build green software applications on Azure</title>
    <link>http://azure.github.io/sustainability/overview/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Overview on Build green software applications on Azure</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Microsoft Open Source Community</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 15:04:29 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://azure.github.io/sustainability/overview/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About this workshop</title>
      <link>http://azure.github.io/sustainability/overview/about-this-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 15:04:29 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://azure.github.io/sustainability/overview/about-this-workshop/</guid>
      <description>This is a technical application workshop with a focus on experiential group learning and collaboration with your peers to solve a customer business problem. You will be strategizing solution considerations to design a robust recommended solution architecture to meet business requirements.
You will work in small groups on a real-life customer scenario that simulates the format of an Architecture Design Session (ADS) to learn how to design and build green software applications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About our commitments</title>
      <link>http://azure.github.io/sustainability/overview/about-our-commitments/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 15:04:29 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://azure.github.io/sustainability/overview/about-our-commitments/</guid>
      <description>At Azure, we consider sustainability and humanity&amp;rsquo;s reaction to climate change to be among the most significant concerns of our time.
We think it&amp;rsquo;s still possible to make plans for a better, cleaner future. To ensure that we are adjusting and expanding alongside the world with the least amount of negative environmental impact, we have committed to putting sustainable technology at the center of our innovation.
Info The Carbon Benefits of Cloud Computing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About green software</title>
      <link>http://azure.github.io/sustainability/overview/about-green-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 15:04:29 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://azure.github.io/sustainability/overview/about-green-software/</guid>
      <description>Software that emits the least amount of carbon is called green software, which is an emerging discipline at the intersection of climate science, software design, electricity markets, hardware, and data center design. Only three activities reduce the carbon emissions of software: energy efficiency, hardware efficiency, and carbon awareness.
Principles Defining, building, and running green software applications requires a core set of competencies (cf. above) called principles. Independent of the application domain, industry, company size or kind, cloud provider or self-hosted, and programming language or framework, they come to a consensus on what it takes to be a green software practitioner.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>